http://www.inlab.de/aboutus/privacy-policy/

Widerrufsrecht
Impressum (Imprint)
General
Your privacy is very important to us. At Inlab Networks we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.
It is Inlab Networks policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Inlab Networks collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.
Inlab Networks purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Inlab Networks visitors use its website. From time to time, Inlab Networks may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Any request to this site is stored in our server’s access log. We may use centralized monitoring services for stability, improvement, alerts and support.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Inlab Networks websites choose to interact with Inlab Networks in ways that require Inlab Networks to gather personally-identifying information.
Those who wish to receive Inlab Networks updates via email, we collect their email addresses.
In each case, Inlab Networks collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Inlab Networks. Inlab Networks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Aggregated Statistics
Inlab Networks may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. For instance, Inlab Networks may monitor the most popular pages on this site.
Inlab Networks may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Inlab Networks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Information We Share
Inlab Networks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Inlab Networks’ behalf or to provide services available at Inlab Networks’ websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Inlab Networks’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.
Inlab Networks will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Inlab Networks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Inlab Networks believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Inlab Networks, third parties or the public at large.
If you have supplied your email address, Inlab Networks may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Inlab Networks and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum.
If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.
Inlab Networks takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information, as discussed below.
Information Security
We work hard to protect our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of information we hold, in particular:
We encrypt many of our services using SSL.
We review our information collection, storage, and processing procedures, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
We restrict access to personal information to Inlab Networks employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.
Cookies
We don’t use or set any cookies on this site.
Business Transfers
If Inlab Networks, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Inlab Networks goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Inlab Networks may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
When this Privacy Policy Applies
Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Inlab Networks and its affiliates, including services Inlab Networks provides on mobile devices, and services offered on other sites, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.
Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including other sites linked to our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.
Compliance and cooperation with regulatory authorities
We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self-regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Inlab Networks may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Inlab Networks’ sole discretion. Inlab Networks encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Contact
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or your dealings with our website, please contact us by clicking
here.
